[
  { "id": "1", "question": "Capital of France", "answer": "Paris" },
  { "id": "2", "question": "Largest mammal", "answer": "Whale" },
  { "id": "3", "question": "Element with symbol 'O'", "answer": "Oxygen" },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "Programming language by Mozilla",
    "answer": "JavaScript"
  },
  { "id": "5", "question": "Earth's natural satellite", "answer": "Moon" },
  { "id": "6", "question": "Primary color", "answer": "Red" },
  { "id": "7", "question": "Founder of Microsoft", "answer": "Bill" },
  { "id": "8", "question": "Insect that produces honey", "answer": "Bee" },
  { "id": "9", "question": "Mount Everest is located in", "answer": "Nepal" },
  { "id": "10", "question": "Universal solvent", "answer": "Water" },
  { "id": "11", "question": "Element with symbol 'Fe'", "answer": "Iron" },
  { "id": "12", "question": "Largest ocean", "answer": "Pacific" },
  { "id": "13", "question": "Smallest prime number", "answer": "Two" },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "Greatest common factor of 12 and 18",
    "answer": "Six"
  },
  { "id": "17", "question": "Element with symbol 'H'", "answer": "Hydrogen" },
  { "id": "18", "question": "Founder of SpaceX", "answer": "Elon" },
  { "id": "19", "question": "Insect known for hard work", "answer": "Ant" },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "Smallest planet in our solar system",
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "question": "Number of continents on Earth",
    "answer": "Seven"
  },
  { "id": "22", "question": "Element with symbol 'C'", "answer": "Carbon" },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "question": "Programming language by Apple",
    "answer": "Swift"
  },
  { "id": "24", "question": "Element with symbol 'N'", "answer": "Nitrogen" },
  { "id": "25", "question": "Our closest star", "answer": "Sun" },
  { "id": "26", "question": "The Red Planet", "answer": "Mars" },
  { "id": "27", "question": "Element with symbol 'K'", "answer": "Potassium" },
  { "id": "28", "question": "Second-largest ocean", "answer": "Atlantic" },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "question": "Programming language by Google",
    "answer": "Python"
  },
  { "id": "30", "question": "Element with symbol 'P'", "answer": "Phosphorus" },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "question": "Hard outer layer of the Earth",
    "answer": "Crust"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "question": "Smallest prime number greater than 10",
    "answer": "Eleven"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "question": "Most abundant gas in the Earth's atmosphere",
    "answer": "Nitrogen"
  },
  { "id": "35", "question": "Element with symbol 'S'", "answer": "Sulfur" },
  { "id": "36", "question": "Founder of Facebook", "answer": "Mark" },
  { "id": "37", "question": "Element with symbol 'Mg'", "answer": "Magnesium" },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "question": "Programming language by Facebook",
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  { "id": "40", "question": "Metal used in pencils", "answer": "Graphite" },
  { "id": "41", "question": "Element with symbol 'Si'", "answer": "Silicon" },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "question": "Largest desert in the world",
    "answer": "Antarctica"
  },
  { "id": "43", "question": "Element with symbol 'Ca'", "answer": "Calcium" },
  { "id": "45", "question": "Element with symbol 'Ar'", "answer": "Argon" },
  { "id": "46", "question": "River in Egypt", "answer": "Nil" },
  { "id": "47", "question": "Metal used in batteries", "answer": "Zinc" },
  { "id": "48", "question": "Element with symbol 'Cl'", "answer": "Chlorine" },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "question": "Programming language by Oracle",
    "answer": "Java"
  },
  { "id": "50", "question": "Largest moon of Saturn", "answer": "Titan" },
  { "id": "51", "question": "Element with symbol 'Ne'", "answer": "Neon" },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "question": "Largest planet in our solar system",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  { "id": "55", "question": "Metal used in airplanes", "answer": "Aluminum" },
  { "id": "56", "question": "Element with symbol 'Na'", "answer": "Sodium" },
  { "id": "57", "question": "Programming language by Google", "answer": "Go" },
  { "id": "58", "question": "Element with symbol 'G'", "answer": "Gold" },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "question": "Second-largest desert in the world",
    "answer": "Arabia"
  },
  { "id": "60", "question": "Element with symbol 'F'", "answer": "Fluorine" },
  { "id": "62", "question": "Programming language by IBM", "answer": "Cobol" },
  { "id": "63", "question": "Element with symbol 'Cu'", "answer": "Copper" },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "question": "Largest island in the world",
    "answer": "Greenland"
  },
  { "id": "65", "question": "Capital of Japan", "answer": "Tokyo" },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "question": "Largest island in Europe",
    "answer": "Britain"
  },
  { "id": "67", "question": "Currency of China", "answer": "Yuan" },
  { "id": "68", "question": "Birthplace of Buddha", "answer": "Lumbini" },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "question": "Longest river in South America",
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  { "id": "70", "question": "Currency of Brazil", "answer": "Real" },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "question": "Country with the most pyramids",
    "answer": "Sudan"
  },
  { "id": "72", "question": "Home of the kangaroo", "answer": "Australia" },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "question": "Largest lake in North America",
    "answer": "Superior"
  },
  { "id": "75", "question": "Birthplace of Mozart", "answer": "Austria" },
  { "id": "76", "question": "Oldest active volcano", "answer": "Etna" },
  { "id": "83", "question": "Country with the most lakes", "answer": "Canada" },
  { "id": "84", "question": "Birthplace of Chopin", "answer": "Poland" },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "question": "Largest island in the Caribbean",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "question": "Birthplace of Leonardo da Vinci",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "question": "Country with the most volcanoes",
    "answer": "Indonesia"
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "question": "Oldest continuously inhabited city",
    "answer": "Damascus"
  },
  { "id": "92", "question": "Largest natural arch", "answer": "Kazakhstan" },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "question": "Country with the most UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage elements",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "question": "Birthplace of Che Guevara",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "question": "Country with the most time zones in a single country",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  { "id": "97", "question": "Birthplace of Confucius", "answer": "China" },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "question": "Country with the most islands in the Pacific",
    "answer": "Sweden"
  },
  { "id": "100", "question": "Birthplace of Shakespeare", "answer": "England" },
  { "id": "103", "question": "Birthplace of Gandhi", "answer": "India" }
]
